Guess it's time,
you better plug in all your nightlights.
What's out there, past your darkened door?
Just the eyes floating up out of the shore.
Hey man, I'm gonna eat your girlfriend,
Or maybe turn her into broth,
la-la-la la la
Kill a kid, cut em up.
Stuff em up inside of my, secret meat box.
Find my, hands across your body slowly
peel your skin off.
You'll meet your friends,
inside the ambulance.
Call into the night,
to the werewolf.
Give all your blood to him,
stand under the warm street light.
Let yourself be hypnotized.
You're just a little snack,
and so is your girlfriend.
Hey man, I'm gonna tear your eyes out,
and then I'll boil your girlfriend,
la-la-la la la
Kill a kid, cut em up.
Stuff em up inside of my, burning dungeon.
I would give you guys a little break but
I'm not Satan.