Your skin is freezing,
here let me help you take it off.
Feasting with your friends,
what a perfect way to end,
all these lonely holidays.
la la la la
Gonna take a piece of your rabies,
and vivisect your mind.
Snowman smiling with your teeth,
fallen angels created with your meat.
That pearly smile.
Cut, in a thousand slices.
Bake you 'til, golden brown.
Stuff you with spices.
Serve to friends around.
Separate, you from your eyes.
Turn your girlfriend inside out,
burn her fingernails.
la la la la
Soak your hands in freezing water.
Watching as the skin gets softer.
See your bones appear in dark red snow...
Drop further below.
Gonna take a piece of your rabies,
and vivisect your mind.
Gonna take a peek inside your head,
and find the worm inside.
Cut, in a thousand slices.
Bake you 'til, golden brown.
Fill you with spices.
Serve to friends around.
Turn the heat on high and we'll reduce your blood...
...boil 'lil Boyfriend...
...with brandy and plums.